<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<node name="/Channel_Type_Server_TLS_Connection"
    xmlns:tp="http://telepathy.freedesktop.org/wiki/DbusSpec#extensions-v0">
  <tp:copyright> Copyright © 2010 Collabora Limited </tp:copyright>
  <tp:license>
    This library is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
    modify it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public
    License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
    version 2.1 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

    This library is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the GNU
    Lesser General Public License for more details.

    You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public
    License along with this library; if not, write to the Free Software
    Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301, USA.
  </tp:license>

  <interface name="org.freedesktop.Telepathy.Channel.Type.ServerTLSConnection.DRAFT"
	     tp:causes-havoc="experimental">

    <tp:requires interface="org.freedesktop.Telepathy.Channel"/>

    <tp:docstring xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
      <p>
      A channel type that carries a TLS certificate between a server
      and a client connecting to it.<br/>
      Channels of this kind are never requested, are anonymous, and SHOULD be
      dispatched while the
      <tp:dbus-ref
      namespace="org.freedesktop.Telepathy">Connection</tp:dbus-ref>
      owning it is in the CONNECTING state.</p>
      <p>In this case, handlers SHOULD accept or reject the certificate, using
      the relevant methods on the provided object, or MAY just close the channel before doing so, to fall
      back to a non-interactive verification process done inside the CM.</p>
      <p>For example, channels of this kind can pop up while a client is
      connecting to an XMPP server.</p>
    </tp:docstring>

    <property name="ServerCertificate" type="o" access="read"
	      tp:name-for-bindings="ServerCertificate">
      <tp:docstring>
	A <tp:dbus-ref
	namespace="org.freedesktop.Telepathy.Authentication">TLSCertificate.DRAFT</tp:dbus-ref>
	containing the certificate chain as sent by the server,
	and other relevant information.
      </tp:docstring>
    </property>

  </interface>
</node>

